<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meirl on Juliya Gannon&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/meirl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meirl on Juliya Gannon&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <copyright>©</copyright>
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/meirl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Redheads and Heavy Network</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/redheads-and-heavy-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/redheads-and-heavy-network/</guid>
      <description>Earlier in the Summer, I decided to create a game studio with my friend, Janine. We were to call it Redheads, which is why you might see a link to it at the bottom of my website.
Unfortunately, things did not pan out. I became overworked and overwhelmed trying to do everything at once. I then decided, what if I restarted Heavy Network - a project dedicated to providing free static websites to local unsigned musicians.</description>
      <content>
  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/fuckingidiot.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;meirl&#34;  /&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the Summer, I decided to create a game studio with my friend, Janine. We were to call it &lt;strong&gt;Redheads&lt;/strong&gt;, which is why you might see a link to it at the bottom of my website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, things did not pan out. I became overworked and overwhelmed trying to do everything at once. I then decided, what if I restarted &lt;strong&gt;Heavy Network&lt;/strong&gt; - a project dedicated to providing free static websites to local &lt;em&gt;unsigned&lt;/em&gt; musicians. I started Heavy in 2017, my first band being &lt;strong&gt;Monte Luna&lt;/strong&gt; in Austin, Texas. Sad to say Monte Luna broke my only rule - that bands remain unsigned to a record label if they wanted my services. Suffice to say I was disheartened after all that. But my dream of helping independent musicians in my city persisted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now I am dedicating my free dev time completely to what I started Heavy Network to do, but without a company or plans to grow or prosper. It will be something I do in my spare time, for nothing at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in a website from me, and are an &lt;em&gt;unsigned&lt;/em&gt; musician in Texas, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:juliyagannon@proton.me&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;email me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Check the homepage on my website to see if I am currently accepting new bands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is no one&amp;rsquo;s fault but my own. I take full accountability for not being able to handle such an intense workload. I was trying to learn everything at once, doing everything at once. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a good system in place for me. But now I do. I realize how important it is that I limit my dev work to only a few days a week to stay sane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In better news, &lt;em&gt;tomorrow I am 12 years sober&lt;/em&gt;! I am celebrating with my husband, Eirik, and my mother (Happy Birthday mom!)
Expect at least one blog post a month from me, maybe ramp it up later. Cause who reads blogs anymore? They&amp;rsquo;re usually lame and boring. I hope you enjoy my blog even if it&amp;rsquo;s just to cringe :D&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
